Guide to the New-York Historical Society Portrait Collection, circa 1640-2020 (bulk, 1800-1950) PR 52
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Individuals and Family Groups
  - Subseries I.A. Individuals and Family Groups: Small Format
    - Carnegie (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carney, Sydney and family (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carnochan (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carpenter (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carpenter, George A. and Harriet I. (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carpenter, Matthew H. (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carr (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carroll (Offsite-box 27)
    - Carter (Offsite-box 27)
    - Cary (Offsite-box 27)
    - Case (Offsite-box 27)
    - Casey (Offsite-box 27)
    - Cass, Lewis (Offsite-box 27)
    - Catlin (Offsite-box 27)
    - Caton (Offsite-box 27)
    - Catt, Carrie Chapman (Offsite-box 27)
    - Chamberlin, Clarence D. (Offsite-box 27)
    - Champe (Offsite-box 27)
    - Chandler (Offsite-box 27)
    - Chapin (Offsite-box 27)
    - Chapin, E. H. (Offsite-box 27)
    - Chase (Offsite-box 28)
    - Chase, Salmon P. (Offsite-box 28)
    - Chase, Samuel (Offsite-box 28)
    - Chase, William Merritt (Offsite-box 28)
    - Cheney (Offsite-box 28)
    - Child (Offsite-box 28)
    - Child, Edmund Bramhall (Offsite-box 28)
    - Childs (Offsite-box 28)
    - Choate, Joseph H. (Offsite-box 28)
    - Choate, Rufus (Offsite-box 28)
    - Christophe, Henri (Offsite-box 28)
    - Church (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clarendon, Edward Hyde (Lord Cornbury) (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clark (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clark, George Rogers (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clarke (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clarkson (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clay (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clay, Henry (Offsite-box 28)
      As a younger man
      As an older man
      Medals, busts, and monument
    - Clay, Henry and wife (Offsite-box 28)
    - Clayton (Offsite-box 29)
    - Clemens, Samuel L. (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cleveland (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cleveland, Frances (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cleveland, Grover (Offsite-box 29)
    - Clinton, DeWitt (Offsite-box 29)
    - Clinton, George (Offsite-box 29)
    - Clinton, George (with original autograph fragment, undated) (Offsite-box 29)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Gift of Jeanette Sarkasian Wagner, February 2019.
    - Clinton, George and wife (Offsite-box 29)
    - Clinton, Henry (Offsite-box 29)
    - Clinton, James (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cobb (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cobb, Howell (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cochran (Offsite-box 29)
    - Cochrane, Thomas (Offsite-box 29)
    - Codrington, Edward (Offsite-box 30)
    - Cody, William F. (Offsite-box 30)
    - Coffin (Offsite-box 30)
    - Coke, Thomas (Offsite-box 30)
    - Colden, Cadwallader (Offsite-box 30)
    - Cole (Offsite-box 30)
    - Colfax, Schuyler (Offsite-box 30)
    - Collingwood, Cuthbert (Offsite-box 30)
    - Collins (Offsite-box 30)
    - Collyer (Offsite-box 30)
    - Columbus, Christopher (2 folders) (Offsite-box 30)
    - Conner (Offsite-box 30)
    - Cook (Offsite-box 30)
    - Cook, James (Offsite-box 30)
    - Cooke (Offsite-box 30)
    - Coolidge, Calvin (Offsite-box 30)
    - Cooper (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cooper, James Fenimore (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cooper, Peter (2 folders) (Offsite-box 31)
    - Corcoran, Michael (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cornell (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cornwallis, Charles Marquis (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cornwallis, William (Offsite-box 31)
    - Couch (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox (2 folders) (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, Eliza Pilcher (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, J. Dolson (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, John Vance (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, Mary Eliza (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, Samuel Hanson (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, Townsend (Offsite-box 31)
    - Cox, Townsend, Jr. (Offsite-box 31)
    - Crane (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crawford (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crawford, Samuel W. (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crawford, William H. (Offsite-box 32)
    - Cresswell, P. M. G. (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crispell, John Bell (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crittenden (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crittenden, J. J. (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crocker (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crocker, Marcellus M. (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crockett, David (Offsite-box 32)
    - Cromwell (Offsite-box 32)
    - Cromwell, Oliver (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crook, George (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crosby (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crosby, Howard (Offsite-box 32)
    - Crosby, John Schuyler (Offsite-box 32)
    - Cruger (Offsite-box 32)
    - Curtin (Offsite-box 33)
    - Curtis (Offsite-box 33)
    - Curtis, George William (Offsite-box 33)
    - Curtis, Roger (Offsite-box 33)
    - Curtis, Samuel R. (Offsite-box 33)
    - Cushing (Offsite-box 33)
    - Cushing, Caleb (Offsite-box 33)
    - Cushing, William B. (Offsite-box 33)
    - Custer, George Armstrong (Offsite-box 33)
    - Cutting (Offsite-box 33)
    - Da-Dz miscellaneous (23 folders) (Offsite-box 34)
    - Dahlgren, John A. (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dahlgren, Ulric (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dale, Richard (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dallas, George M. (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dana, Charles A. (Offsite-box 37)
    - Danforth (Offsite-box 37)
    - Davidson (Offsite-box 37)
    - Davie (Offsite-box 37)
    - Davies (Offsite-box 37)
    - Davis (Offsite-box 37)
    - Davis, Jefferson (Offsite-box 37)
    - Davis, Jefferson Columbus (Offsite-box 37)
    - David, Charles H. (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dawes, Charles (Offsite-box 37)
    - Day (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dayton, William L. (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dean (Offsite-box 37)
    - Dean, Silas (Offsite-box 37)
    - DeKay, James E. (Offsite-box 37)
    - Delacroix (Offsite-box 37)
    - Delafield (Offsite-box 37)
    - Delano (Offsite-box 37)
    - DeLoosey (see Havemeyer/deLoosey family) (Offsite-box 37)
    - Depew, Chauncey (Offsite-box 37)
    - De Peyster (Offsite-box 38)
    - De Peyster, Abraham and wife (Offsite-box 38)
    - Derby (Offsite-box 38)
    - Deven, Charles (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dewey, George (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dewey, Thomas (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dewitt (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dexter (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dickinson (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dickinson, John (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dix (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dix, John A. (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dodge (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dodge, Grenville N. (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dodge, William E. (Offsite-box 38)
    - Dorr (Offsite-box 38)
    - Doubleday, Abner (Offsite-box 38)
    - Douglas (Offsite-box 39)
    - Douglas, Stephen A. (Offsite-box 39)
    - Downing (Offsite-box 39)
    - Doyle (Offsite-box 39)
    - Drake, Francis (Offsite-box 39)
    - Draper (Offsite-box 39)
    - Drayton (Offsite-box 39)
    - Drayton, P. (Offsite-box 39)
    - Drayton, W. H. (Offsite-box 39)
    - Drowne (Offsite-box 39)
    - Dubois (Offsite-box 39)
    - Duckworth, John Thomas (Offsite-box 39)
    - Dudley (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dudley, Horace E. (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dudley, Horace E., family (Offsite-box 40)
    - Duff (Offsite-box 40)
    - Duffy, James Edmund (Offsite-box 40)
    - Duke, Tony (Offsite-box 40)
    - Duncan, Adam (Viscount Duncan) (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dunlap (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dunsmore, John Ward (Offsite-box 40)
      In costume
      In studio, exhibition and studios
      Portraits, general
      Self-portraits (photographs of paintings)
    - Dupont, Samuel F. (Offsite-box 40)
    - Durand (Offsite-box 40)
    - Duryee, Abram (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dutcher (Offsite-box 40)
    - Duyckinck (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dwight (Offsite-box 40)
    - Dyer (Offsite-box 40)
    - Ea-Ez miscellaneous (9 folders) (Offsite-box 41)
    - Eames, Wilberforce (Offsite-box 42)
    - Early, Jubal (Offsite-box 42)
    - Eaton (Offsite-box 42)
    - Eddy (Offsite-box 42)
    - Edison, Thomas Alva and Mina (Offsite-box 42)
    - Edmunds (Offsite-box 42)
    - Edwards (Offsite-box 42)
    - Edwards, George Wharton (Offsite-box 42)
    - Edwards, Jonathan (Offsite-box 42)
    - Egan, William Bradshaw (Offsite-box 42)
    - Eglinton (Offsite-box 42)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Offsite-box 42)
    - Eliot, Charles W. (Offsite-box 42)
    - Eliott, George Augustus (Lord Heathfield) (Offsite-box 42)
    - Ellett, Charles (Offsite-box 42)
    - Elliott (Offsite-box 42)
    - Ellis (Offsite-box 42)
    - Ellsworth, Elmer E. (Offsite-box 43)
    - Ellsworth, Oliver (Offsite-box 43)
    - Elsberg, Louis (Offsite-box 43)
    - Elphinstone, George Keith (Offsite-box 43)
    - Ely (Offsite-box 43)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo (Offsite-box 43)
    - Emmett, Thomas Addis (Offsite-box 43)
    - English (Offsite-box 43)
    - English, William H. (Offsite-box 43)
    - Ericsson, John (Offsite-box 43)
    - Erskine (Offsite-box 43)
    - Evans (Offsite-box 43)
    - Evans, Robley D. (Offsite-box 43)
    - Evarts, William M. (Offsite-box 43)
    - Everett, Edward (Offsite-box 43)
    - Ewell, Richard (Offsite-box 43)
    - Ewing (Offsite-box 43)
    - Fa-Fz miscellaneous (19 folders) (Offsite-box 44)
    - Fairbanks (Offsite-box 46)
    - Fairchild (Offsite-box 46)
    - Fairfax (Offsite-box 46)
    - Fanning (Offsite-box 46)
    - Farmer, Sarah I. (Offsite-box 46)
    - Farnham (Offsite-box 46)
    - Farragut, David Glasgow (Offsite-box 46)
      Monuments and memorials
      Portraits
    - Farrar (Offsite-box 46)
    - Fenton, Reuben (Offsite-box 46)
    - Ferguson (Offsite-box 46)
    - Ferris (Offsite-box 46)
    - Ferry (Offsite-box 46)
    - Fessenden (Offsite-box 46)
    - Field (Offsite-box 46)
    - Field, Cyrus West (Offsite-box 46)
    - Fillmore, Millard (Offsite-box 46)
    - Finley (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fish (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fish, Hamilton (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fish, Nicholas (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fish, Stuyvesant and Marian (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fisher (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fisk (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fitch (Offsite-box 47)
    - Fletcher (Offsite-box 47)
    - Flower (Offsite-box 47)
    - Floyd (Offsite-box 47)
    - Foch, Ferdinand (Offsite-box 47)
    - Foote (Offsite-box 47)
    - Forbes (Offsite-box 47)
    - Ford (Offsite-box 47)
    - Forrest (Offsite-box 47)
    - Forrest, N. B. (Offsite-box 47)
    - Forsyth (Offsite-box 47)
    - Foster (Offsite-box 48)
    - Foster, John G. (Offsite-box 48)
    - Foster, Stephen (Offsite-box 48)
    - Fowler (Offsite-box 48)
    - Fox (Offsite-box 48)
    - Fox, Charles James (Offsite-box 48)
    - Francis, John W. (Offsite-box 48)
    - Francis, Joseph (Offsite-box 48)
    - Franklin (Offsite-box 48)
    - Franklin, Benjamin (Offsite-box 48)
      Bust-length portraits with glasses
      Bust-length portraits without glasses
      Embossed paper portraits
      Full-length portraits
      Scenes from life
      Sculpture – busts
      Sculpture – full-length
    - Franklin, John (Offsite-box 49)
    - Franklin, William B. (Offsite-box 49)
    - Franks, Jacob and family (Offsite-box 49)
    - Frelinghuysen, Theodore (Offsite-box 49)
    - Fremont, John C. (Offsite-box 49)
    - French (Offsite-box 49)
    - Fry (Offsite-box 49)
    - Fulton, Robert (Offsite-box 49)
    - Fuller (Offsite-box 49)
    - Furman (Offsite-box 49)
    - Ga-Gz miscellaneous (# folders?) (Offsite-box 50)
    - Gage, Thomas (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gagner family (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gaines, Edmund Pendleton (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gallatin (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gallatin, Albert (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gallatin, Albert Eugene (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gallatin, Frederic (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gansevoort (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gardiner (Offsite-box 53)
    - Gardner, Alan (Offsite-box 53)
    - Garfield, James A. (Offsite-box 53)
    - Garfield, Lucretia Rudolph (Offsite-box 53)
    - Garibaldi, Guiseppe (Offsite-box 53)
    - Garland (Offsite-box 53)
    - Garrett (Offsite-box 54)
    - Garrison, William Lloyd (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gates (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gates, Horatio (Offsite-box 54)
    - Genet (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gerry, Elbridge (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gibson (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gilbert (Offsite-box 54)
      Related Materials
      For a group portrait of a dinner thrown by F.W. Woolworth in honor of architect Cass Gilbert, see Subseries II.B. Groups: Medium format, Commercial activities, Businesses.
    - Gillmore, Quincy A. (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gilman (Offsite-box 54)
    - Girard, Stephen (Offsite-box 54)
    - Gladstone, William Ewart (Offsite-box 54)
    - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von (Offsite-box 55)
    - Goldsborough, Louis M. (Offsite-box 55)
    - Goldsmith, Oliver (Offsite-box 55)
    - Goodwin (Offsite-box 55)
    - Gordon (Offsite-box 55)
    - Gordon, John B. (Offsite-box 55)
    - Gough, John B. (Offsite-box 55)
    - Gould (Offsite-box 55)
    - Gould, Helen and children (Offsite-box 55)
    - Gould, Jay (Offsite-box 55)
    - Graham (Offsite-box 55)
    - Granger (Offsite-box 55)
    - Grant (Offsite-box 55)
    - Grant, Frederick D. and family (Offsite-box 55)
    - Grant, Hugh (Offsite-box 55)
    - Grant, Ulysses S. (Offsite-box 56)
      Album of his life, circa 1886
      Funeral procession, 1885 August 8
      ....As military officer and in uniform: photographs
      ....As military officer and in uniform: prints
      ....As President and civilian: photographs
      ....As President and civilian: prints
      ....In uniform with full beard, 1861
      ....With family members
      ....With family - group portraits and homes
      Tombs and memorial photographs
    - Graves (Offsite-box 57)
    - Gray (Offsite-box 57)
    - Greeley, Horace (Offsite-box 57)
    - Green (Offsite-box 57)
    - Greene (Offsite-box 57)
    - Greene, George Sears (Offsite-box 57)
    - Greene, Nathaniel (Offsite-box 57)
    - Gregg (Offsite-box 57)
    - Gregory (Offsite-box 57)
    - Gresham, Walter O. (Offsite-box 57)
    - Griffin (Offsite-box 57)
    - Griffith (Offsite-box 57)
    - Griffith, Frederick (Offsite-box 57)
    - Griswold (Offsite-box 58)
    - Grosvenor (Offsite-box 58)
    - Grover (Offsite-box 58)
    - Grundy, Felix (Offsite-box 58)
    - Guggenheim (Offsite-box 58)
    - Gunn (Offsite-box 58)
    - Gunther (Offsite-box 58)
    - Gurney (Offsite-box 58)
    - Ha-Hz miscellaneous (31 folders) (Offsite-box 59)
    - Habersham (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hale (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hale, Edward Everett (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hale, Nathan (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hall (Offsite-box 62)
    - Halleck, Fitz-Green (Offsite-box 62)
    - Halleck, Henry W. (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hamilton (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hamilton, Alexander (Offsite-box 62)
      Sculpture
    - Hamilton, Elizabeth Schuyler (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hamlin, Hannibal (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hammond (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hampton, Wade (Offsite-box 62)
    - Hancock, John (Offsite-box 63)
    - Hancock, Winfield Scott (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harbord, J. G. (Offsite-box 63)
    - Hardee, William J. (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harding, Warren Gamaliel (Offsite-box 63)
    - Hardinge (Offsite-box 63)
    - Hardy (Offsite-box 63)
    - Hardy, Charles (Offsite-box 63)
    - Hare (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harlan (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harle (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harmon (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harper (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harris (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harrison (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harrison, Benjamin and family (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harrison, William Henry and Anna Symmes (Offsite-box 63)
    - Harsen (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hart (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hastings (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hatch (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hauptmann (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hawke, Edward (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hawley (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hay (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hay, John (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hayes (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hayes, Rutherford B. and Lucy (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hayne (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hays (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hazen, W. B. (Offsite-box 64)
    - Heathcote, Caleb (Offsite-box 64)
    - Heintzelman, Samuel P. (Offsite-box 64)
    - Hendricks, Thomas A. (Offsite-box 64)
    - Henry (Offsite-box 65)
    - Henry, Patrick (Offsite-box 65)
    - Henry, Thomas S. and wives (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hervey (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hewitt (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hewitt, Abram Stevens (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hickok, Wild Bill (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hicks (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hicks, Elias (Offsite-box 65)
    - Higgins (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hill (2 folders) (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hill, A. P. (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hitchcock, E. A. (Offsite-box 65)
    - Hobart (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hobson, Richmond Pearson (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hodges (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hoffman (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hoffman, Eugene A. (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hoffman, John T. (Offsite-box 66)
    - Holden (Offsite-box 66)
    - Holland (Offsite-box 66)
    - Holmes (Offsite-box 66)
    - Holmes, Louise Allen (Offsite-box 66)
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (Offsite-box 66)
    - Holt (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hone, Philip (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hood (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hood, Alexander (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hood, John B. (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hood, Samuel (Offsite-box 66)
    - Hooker, Joseph (Offsite-box 67)
    - Hoover, Herbert Clark (Offsite-box 67)
    - Hopkins (Offsite-box 67)
    - Hopkins, Ellen Dunlap (Offsite-box 67)
    - Hopkinson (Offsite-box 67)
    - Hosmer (Offsite-box 67)
    - Hotchkiss (Offsite-box 67)
    - Houston (Offsite-box 67)
    - Houston, Samuel (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howard (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howard, Charles (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howard, Harry (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howard, Oliver O. (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howe (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howe, Richard (Offsite-box 67)
    - Howell (Offsite-box 68)
    - Howells (Offsite-box 68)
    - Howland (Offsite-box 68)
    - Howland, Henry Elias (2 folders) (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hoyt (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hubbard (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hubbard, Gurdon S. and wife (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hudson (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hughes (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hughes, Charles Evans (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hughes, Edward (Offsite-box 68)
    - Hull (Offsite-box 69)
    - Humboldt, Alexander von (Offsite-box 69)
    - Humphrey (Offsite-box 69)
    - Humphreys (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hunt (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hunter (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hunter, David (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hunter, Robert M. T. (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hunter, Thomas (Offsite-box 69)
    - Huntington (Offsite-box 69)
    - Huntington, Samuel (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hutton (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hyacinthe, Pere (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hyde (Offsite-box 69)
    - Hyde, James Hazen (Offsite-box 69)
      James Hazen Hyde and related photos removed to Hyde Papers, December 2019.
    - Ia-Iz miscellaneous (3 folders) (Offsite-box 70)
    - Ingalls (Offsite-box 70)
    - Ingersoll (Offsite-box 70)
    - Ingersoll, Robert (Offsite-box 70)
    - Inman (Offsite-box 70)
    - Irving, Washington (Offsite-box 70)
    - Irwin (Offsite-box 70)
    - Ives (Offsite-box 70)
    - Ja-Jz miscellaneous (7 folders) (Offsite-box 71)
    - Jackson (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jackson, Andrew (2 folders) (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jackson, James (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jackson, Stonewall (Thomas J.) (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jackson, William Hicks (Offsite-box 72)
    - James (Offsite-box 72)
    - James, Arthur C. (Offsite-box 72)
    - James, D. Willis and Ellen (Offsite-box 72)
    - James, Henry (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jay (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jay, John (Offsite-box 72)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (3 folders) (Offsite-box 73)
    - Jenkins (Offsite-box 73)
    - Jensen, Gustav (Offsite-box 73)
    - Joan of Arc (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnson (2 folders) (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnson, Andrew and Eliza (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnson, Hosmer A. (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnson, Reverdy (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnson, Samuel (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnson, William (Offsite-box 73)
    - Johnston (Offsite-box 74)
    - Johnston, Albert S. (Offsite-box 74)
    - Johnston, Joseph Eggleston (Offsite-box 74)
    - Jones (2 folders) (Offsite-box 74)
    - Jones, Catesby (Offsite-box 74)
    - Jones, Jacob (Offsite-box 74)
    - Jones, John Paul (Offsite-box 74)
      Sculptures, scenes from life, etc.
    - Jones, Samuel J. (Offsite-box 74)
    - Jordan (Offsite-box 74)
    - Jouett, James E. (Offsite-box 74)
    - Judd, Norman B. (Offsite-box 74)
    - Judson (Offsite-box 74)
    - Ka-Kz miscellaneous (11 folders) (Offsite-box 75)
    - Kalbfleisch (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kane (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kearny (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kearny, Philip (Offsite-box 76)
    - Keats (Offsite-box 76)
    - Keene (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kelby (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kelley (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kellogg (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kelly (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kempenfelt, Richard (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kendall (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kendall, William Sargeant (Offsite-box 76)
    - Kendrick, Henry Lane (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kennedy (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kennedy, John P. (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kent, James (Offsite-box 77)
    - Keppel, Augustus (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kerfoot (Offsite-box 77)
    - Keteltas (Offsite-box 77)
    - Key (Offsite-box 77)
    - Keyes, Erasmus D. (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kilpatrick, Judson (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kimball (Offsite-box 77)
    - Kimball, Le Roy E. (Offsite-box 77)
    - King (2 folders) (Offsite-box 78)
    - King, Charles (Offsite-box 78)
    - King, Rufus and Mary Alsop (Offsite-box 78)
    - Kip (Offsite-box 78)
    - Kirk (Offsite-box 78)
    - Knapp (Offsite-box 78)
    - Knight (Offsite-box 78)
    - Knox (Offsite-box 78)
    - Knox, Henry (Offsite-box 78)
    - Koch, Edward (Offsite-box 78)
    - Koehn/Kolhn family (Offsite-box 78)
    - Kosciuszko, Thaddeus (Offsite-box 78)
    - Kossuth, Louis (Offsite-box 78)
    - Kretsch (Offsite-box 78)
    - La-Lz miscellaneous (19 folders) (Offsite-box 79)
    - Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves Roch Gilbert Du Motier, marquis de (3 folders) (Offsite-box 81)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorello (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lamar, Lucius Quintus Cincinnatus (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lamb (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lamont (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lander, Frederick W. (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lane (Offsite-box 81)
    - Langdon (Offsite-box 81)
    - Langdon, John (Offsite-box 81)
    - La Rochefoucauld-Liancourt, Francois-Alexandre-Frederic, duc de (Offsite-box 81)
    - Laurence (Offsite-box 81)
    - Laurence, Abbott (Offsite-box 81)
    - Laurens, Henry (Offsite-box 81)
    - Law (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lawrence (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lawrence, James (Offsite-box 81)
    - Lebrun, Albert, Madame (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lee (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lee, Fitzhugh (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lee, Henry (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lee, Robert E. (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lehman (Offsite-box 82)
    - Leland (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lentilhon (Offsite-box 82)
    - Leonard (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lequier family (Offsite-box 82)
    - Levy (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lewis (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lewis, Morgan (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lexow, Clarence (Offsite-box 82)
    - Lincoln, Abraham (Offsite-box 83)
      Death and funeral processions
      Memorials, tributes, caricatures, and allegorical prints
      McClure Collection portfolios
      Photographs
      Prints
      ....Ephemera
      ....Portraits: bust-length without beard
      ....Portraits: bust-length with beard
      ....Portraits: group, with cabinet members
      ....Portraits: group, with family members
      ....Portraits: profile
      ....Portraits: seated
      ....Portraits: standing
      ....Portraits: photographs (19th century) of prints
      Residences
      ....Illinois
      ....Kentucky
      Scenes from the life of
      Twentieth-century portraits
    - Lincoln, Abraham (continued) (Offsite-box 84)
      Bagoe Collection of mounted and captioned copy photographs
      ....Loose (unmounted) photographs
      ....Youth and early life
      ....Political career
      ....Civil War scenes
      ....Gettysburg dedication (1863)
      ....Assassination at Ford's Theatre/deathbed scenes
    - Lincoln, Abraham (continued) (Offsite-box 85)
      Bagoe Collection of mounted and captioned copy photographs (continued)
      ....Funeral and tomb
      ........Processions, train, etc.
      ........New York City scenes